No.
It's beyond all help.
Only Jesus can help.
Jesus - Anders has a navel.
Yes - which collects incredible amounts of cotton.
Well it is not something unnatural.
No, that's what he says.
I've never had ... I just want to say for the record that I've never had ...
I have never looked down, pulled up my sweater and seen a little lint in the navel.
But the thing is that I have hair on my stomach.
That's what does it.
Everyone who has hair on the stomach,
Regardless of the gender, which has a tshirt or shirt will have lint here.
I promise
Well then I would like to know down here in the comments section.
If it is true that all of you who have hair on your stomach, you also have large amounts of lint
It curls out under the sweater
What are you doing now - I'm looking.
Check this out!
Well it starts there.
It is starting to gather now.
And so my hair works.
But there is grass there!
Yes, I don't know where it comes from.
It feels like you are doing such ultrasound as
If we are to finish there The Extended version you can find on the snake pit.
Hahaha
Sorry about..?
This video.
Why?
Yes, yes, actually.
Sorry.
Fy fuck what disgusting it was
Thank you for checking today.
See you again next week.
Take care of yourselves
Kiss and hug -Ciao!